bharattaxi.com 2019-04-17

# 

Bharat Taxi respects your privacy and recognizes the need to protect your personal information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address) you have provided at the time of booking. Bharat Taxi intends to make clear its intention on collecting your data. Generally at the time of booking you don’t have to provide any personally identifiable data except name, phone number. However, there will be some limitations on site usage regarding special offers, discounts etc.  
 **WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**  
When you choose to avail our services, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.  
Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.  
 **CONSENT**  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.  
 **HOW DO I WITHDRAW MY CONSENT?**  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at bharattaxi.com or mailing us at support@bharattaxi.com  
 **DISCLOSURE**  
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.  
 **THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**  
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.  
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  
As an example, if you are located in India and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the outside India, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under that particular country’s norms.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.   
**SECURITY**  
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  
 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
Bharat Taxi reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
